# **RESUME**

Please be noted that the C.V was written by the candidate and printed in HRnavi letterhead only

## VŨ THÁI SƠN (No. 37628)

#### Team Leader

#### PROFILE

Birthday: 1990-05-19 (31 years old)

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Married

Nationality: Vietnamese

Province/City: Thai Binh

District: Vu Thu

Expected salary (Gross): 1,500 - 2,000 USD

Working place: Ha Noi

Start working day: 2 weeks after recruited



Ms. Nguyen Thi Trang Consultant



(+84) 0946.078.299



HCM office, 8<sup>th</sup> floor, Secoin Tower, 9 D2 Str, Sai Gon Pearl., Binh Thanh Dist, HCMC, Vietnam



nguyen.thi.trang@hrnavi.com



Hanoi office, 7<sup>th</sup> floor, Indochina Plaza Hanoi, Office Tower, 241 Xuan Thuy Str., Cau Giay Dist., Hanoi, Vietnam.

#### SKILL

English: Basic (Self-Evaluation)

#### EDUCATION

#### 2008-10 ~ 2012-10: Ho Chi Minh City University of Industry

Country: Viet Nam

Level: University

Major: Computer Science

Ranking: Average

#### WORK EXPERIENCE (9 years 7 months)

#### 2019-04 ~ Present (2 years): DTT

Workplace: Viet Nam - Ha Noi

Position: Group Leader

Job title: Team Leader

#### 2018-06 ~ 2019-04 (10 months): FPT-IS (TSD)

Workplace: Viet Nam - Ha Noi

Position: Staff

Job title: Officer, Team Leader

#### 2015-09 ~ 2018-06 (2 years 9 months): DTT

Workplace: Viet Nam - Ha Noi

Position: Staff

Job title: Team Leader, dev

#### 2013-06 ~ 2015-08 (2 years 2 months): Formos

Workplace: Viet Nam - Ho Chi Minh

Position: Staff

Job title: dev



#### PROFESSIONAL HR CONSULTING SERVICE

### 2011-08 ~ 2013-06 (1 year 10 months): Công ty TTHH Phần mềm Minh Thiên

Workplace: Viet Nam - Ho Chi Minh

Position: Staff

Job title: dev